KONRAD LITWINOWICZ

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT

Hi, my name is Konrad.

I work at DFIN as a Support Software Engineer in an R&D project. At work I deal with the creation of new functionalities, development of current ones, correcting bugs, etc.

During the week and on weekends , I work at GOITeens as a programming trainer. I teach kids from 9-12 years old programming in: MInecraft. I spend most of my days on programming, learning new things, playing video games and sports.

EXPERIENCE

MINECRAFT PROGRAMMING TRAINER
GolTeens Polska | January 2023 - Currently

SUPPORT SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/ JUNIOR DEVELOPER Donnelley Financial Solutions (DFIN)| January 2023 - Currently

JUNIOR DEVELOPER Unit4 | June 2022 - January 2023

INTERN DEVELOPER
Sygnity S.A. | February 2022 - May 2022

PROGRAMMING COACH
Giganci Programowania | February 2022 - December 2022

MINECRAFT PROGRAMMING TRAINER EduGO P.S.A. | September 2021 - February 2022

EDUCATION

MASTER'S DEGREE, TECHNICAL INFORMATICS

Wrocław University of Science and Technology | 2021 - 2023 (Currently)

BACHELOR'S DEGREE, INDUSTRIAL COMPUTER SCIENCE

Wrocław University of Science and Technology | 2017 - 2021

SKILLS

- C#
- ASP.NET
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT.JS
- HTML5
- SQL
- MONGODB
- NODE.JS
- GITHUB
- AZURE
- DEVOPS
- -.NET CORE
- -MS SQL SERVER

OTHERS

- English B2,2
- Readiness to learn
- Self-organization of work
- Communicativeness
- Creativity
- Ability to work in a team
- Good organization of working time
- Ability to share knowledge

CONTACT

E: konrad.litwinowicz@gmail.com

T: +48 536287223

G: https://github.com/Sendej7

G: https://github.com/BrightBitsTech

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).